

HOW TO

- +38 (063) 315 31 67
- Vyshneve, Kiev region
- strizgsergey@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/stryzg-sergii
- S stryzhlucky
- https://github.com/SeregaLucky

SOFT SKILLS

- Problem solving
- Tenacity
- I like challenging tasks
- Teamwork
- Thoroughness
- Perseverance
- Patience

LANGUAGES

English - Intermediate

HOBBIES

- Sport
- Programming

SERGII STRYZH

FRONT-END DEVELOPER (REACT.js)

PERSONAL PROFILE

Web-development has always interesting me and that's why I enjoy my job every day. During my work, I always think about pleasant user experience as well as cleanness and readability of my code. I would be glad to bring value to my future team and continuously develop my technical skills at work.

SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3, SASS (SCSS)
- Javascript, TypeScript
- React.js
- Redux, React-query
- Redux-Thunk, Redux-Saga
- Gulp, Webpack, Parcel

- Npm
- Node.js
- Bootstrap4
- Figma, Photoshop
- Git
- BEM
- Scrum, Jira

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Mentor in one IT training center

2020 - present

Directions: Javascript and React.js

Front-end developer

2021

Created a small shop to order personal business cards.

- developing, building and maintaining the project with React.js and Redux, Redux-Thunk from the ground up

Front-end developer

Betbureau | June 2020 - October 2021

Betting Industry Company that offers a new gambling platform for Ukrainian and Kenyan Market (ongoing development).

- developing, building and maintaining the project with React.js and TypeScript, Redux, Redux-Saga from the ground up
- creating a visually appealing, adaptive web application that works well across different browsers, devices, and platforms.

Front-end developer

Axiom | February 2022 - March 2023

Betting Industry Company that offers a new gambling platform. And created a CMS for this platform.

- developing, building and maintaining the projects with React.js.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

KYIV NATIONAL ECONOMICS UNIVERSITY

Higher economic education. Master's degree in Finance and Credit.

2009-2013

FULL-STACK COURSES

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, Node.js.

2019-2020